Ah, hello.
あ、こんにちは
Is this your first time at this store?
この店初めてですか?
It's my first time.
初めてです
Where does it hurt?
どこが痛いですか?
My waist.
腰とか
Would you like to get a massage?
マッサージ貰おうことあります?
ERROR
たまに貰ってもらいますね
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
How did you find this store?
どうやってこの店見つけたの?
on the internet.
インターネットで
First of all, please get some sleep.
まず最初、ちょっと寝てください
Where is it headed?
どこ向けですか?
Now, wait a minute, unplug everything,
今はちょっと待ってて、全部抜いて、
Cut this.
これを切ったり
Can I come in?
入っていいですか?
Is it hard?
固いですか?
Can I use cutting?
切ったりは使えますか?
You can use it.
使えます
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
that's right.
そうです
Does it feel this good?
こんなに気持ちいいですか?
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
It hurts softly.
そっと痛い
I can't see it, but
見えないけど、
Waist.
腰
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Feels good
気持ちいい
is.
です
Is it special?
特別 ですか?
Is this special?
これ特別?
It might feel good.
気持ちいいかも
Is there meat in it?
肉が入った?
I can't see it.
見えない
over there.
あそこ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can you do it?
できるかな?
Great, great, great.
えらい、えらい、えらい
over there.
あそこ
It's all in.
全部入ったよ
It's too much.
すぎだよ
That's too much.
すぎね
It's all in.
全部入ったよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I'll do the final challenge.
最後のチャレンジやるよ
最後
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
it hurts.
痛い
Please sit down.
座ってください
different.
違う
About 2 minutes.
2分くらい
The entrance hurts.
入り口が痛い
Entrance?
入り口?
It's probably okay.
多分大丈夫
This pose lasts about 1 minute.
このポーズは1分くらい
My head is too strong.
頭が強すぎる
over there.
あそこ
Aso
あそ
child.
こ
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Please sit down.
座ってください